【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 3]
[第3集]
Master, are you okay?
少爷，你还好吗？
Master.
少爷。
I'm fine.
我没事。
How is she today?
她今天怎么样？
she's fine. Miss He and He San went to the horse market together.
她很好。何小姐 和何三一起去了马市。
General He has just arrived at the mansion.
贺将军刚刚 抵达府邸。
He brought several Turkish horses with him.
他带来了几匹土耳其马。
It must be a gift from the lady. Hey.
一定是小姐送的礼物。嘿。
She sends a letter every day.
她每天都会寄一封信。
She is always thinking of you.
她总是想着你。
I'm going to visit the General's Mansion.
我要去参观将军府。
it's getting dark.
天快黑了。
Now is not a good time.
现在不是好时机。
Master, why don't you wait until tomorrow?
少爷， 要不等到明天吧？
When Miss He sends me a letter tomorrow ,
明天何小姐 给我寄信时，
You can simply respond.
你可以简单地回应。
if we leave now
如果我们现在就走
Maybe we can't see it.
也许我们看不到它。
It's not that I want to see her.
并不是我想见她。
I just wanted to be close to her.
我只是想靠近她。
Even just a little closer.
哪怕只是再近一点点。
enough.
足够的。
I can't believe you're laughing at me.
我不敢相信你在嘲笑我。
Master taught me a lot.
师父教会了我很多东西。
I can't even cancel the wedding.
我什至不能取消婚礼。
If you want to apply what the teacher taught you,
如果你想运用老师教给你的东西，
I should kill Rong Yu.
我应该杀了容羽。
How can you say that?
你怎么能这么说呢？
How can you take it seriously?
你怎么能认真对待它呢？
I was joking.
我是开玩笑的。
It's not funny.
这不好笑。
I really miss my days in Wuhuashan.
真怀念 在五华山的日子。
At that time, you always cooked terrible meals for me.
那时候， 你总是给我做难吃的饭菜。
When the master taught me how to make medicine,
当师傅教我 炼药时，
He always comes up with weird ways to torture me.
他总是想出一些 奇怪的方法来折磨我。
And I deal with scorpions and centipedes every day.
而且每天都和蝎子、蜈蚣打交道。
but i have nothing
但我什么都没有
how to worry
如何担心
I thought it was simple.
我以为这很简单。
Quando chegou ao Monte Wuhua,
Quando chegou ao Monte Wuhua,
She is as sick as an old woman.
她像个老妇人一样病了。
You always say you want to go up the mountain and catch birds.
你总说要上山 抓鸟。
Or jump into the river and fish.
或者跳进河里钓鱼。
Whenever I let my guard down, you disappear.
每当我放松警惕， 你就消失了。
you make me so angry
你让我如此生气
Who wants to tie you up with a rope.
谁想用绳子绑住你。
When you recover, you become even more shameful.
当你康复后， 你变得更加可耻。
You said Master was playing tricks on you.
你说师父 在玩你。
Have you forgotten how you played a trick on your master?
你忘了你是如何捉弄你的主人的吗？
So, it’s not like I haven’t had problems.
所以， 我并不是没有遇到过问题。
But he hasn't found them yet.
但他还没有找到他们。
Only children have no problem.
只有孩子没有问题。
I promise you that in a few years you will be living a peaceful life.
我向你保证几年后你会过上平静的生活。
Don't say stupid things.
不要说傻话。
Keep in touch with me and the master.
跟我和师傅保持联系。
After you left Wuhuashan a few years ago,
几年前你离开五华山之后
and travel around the world,
并环游世界，
Master and I almost turned into stone waiting for you.
我和师父差点变成 石头等着你。
We want to send a letter but don't know where to send it.
我们想寄信， 但不知道寄到哪里。
I had no one to talk to when I felt wronged .
当我感到委屈时， 我没有人可以诉说。
These few years.
这几年。
Ling, no matter what happens,
凌，无论发生什么，
You will always be my most beloved sister.
你永远是 我最疼爱的妹妹。
This won't happen again.
以后不会再发生这样的事了。
If you feel aggrieved
如果你觉得委屈的话
Please let me help.
请让我帮忙。
Could it be?
可能是吗？
why not?
为什么不？
Use your wisdom,
用你的智慧，
Every problem can be solved.
每个问题都可以解决。
【Master Zhirong】
【致容师傅】
Unconditional kindness is to satisfy evil.
无条件的仁慈 是为了满足邪恶。
Does he like me?
他喜欢我？
If you feel you've been cheated,
如果你感觉自己被骗了，
let me help you. he can?
我来帮你。他可以？
Why don't I let it?
我为什么不让呢？
Use your wisdom,
用你的智慧，
Every problem can be solved.
每个问题都可以解决。
What if they propose to you?
如果他们向你求婚怎么办？
Isn't it just jumping from one hell to another?
不就是 从一个地狱跳到另一个地狱吗？
You have to marry someone you know.
你必须嫁给你认识的人。
Someone with whom they have a mutual understanding, right?
与他们有 相互理解的人，对吗？
What if that person is me?
如果那个人是我怎么办？
Don't wait.
不要等。
He said it was only a matter of time.
他说这只是时间问题。
We'll talk after I cancel the wedding.
我取消婚礼后我们再谈。
I'd better get engaged to him first.
我最好先跟他订婚。
It would be great if it were him.
如果是他的话，那该多好。
Big brother is very good to me. He has superb martial arts skills.
大哥对我很好。 他有着高超的武术技巧。
Everything about it is good.
关于它的一切都很好。
I'd better lie to my brother to get married.
我最好骗我 哥哥结婚。
why not?
为什么不？
I'm really a bad girl!
我真的是一个坏女孩！
Rong Yu, you idiot.
容宇你个白痴。
You ruined my relationship with my brother.
你毁了我 和哥哥的关系。
If my sister were here
如果我姐姐在的话
Will she help me?
她会帮助我吗？
Young boss.
年轻的老板。
miss. He looked drunk.
错过。他看上去喝醉了。
go.
去。
Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。
I'll call you
我打电话给你
With my thoughts?
与我的想法？
Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。
Do you want to run away again?
你还想再逃跑吗？
SEM opportunities.
SEM机会。
She bullied him again
她又欺负他了
I need to save it.
我需要保存它。
you.
你。
Don't think you can escape.
别以为你能逃走。
Ms. He.
何女士。
European Union...
欧洲联盟...
I won't run away. I just don't think we should touch each other.
我不会逃跑。 我只是觉得我们不应该互相碰触。
You are afraid of me.
你怕我。
No.
不。
Do not move.
不要动。
Didn't I convince her enough?
难道我说服她的还不够吗？
I've never been so patient with anyone.
我从来没有对任何人这么有耐心。
Since childhood.
从小。
Why didn't you show up when I asked?
我问的时候你怎么没出现？
You know we need to talk.
你知道我们需要谈谈。
you think
您认为
Call me a devil?
说我是恶魔？
That's my fault.
那是我的错。
It's your fault.
这是你的错。
You're making things complicated now.
你现在让事情变得复杂了。
Why do you want to propose to me so badly?
你为什么这么想向我求婚？
And then blame me for it.
然后为此责备我。
I didn't say that.
我没那么说过。
How could you say such a thing in front of Master Rong?
你怎么可以 在荣爷面前说这样的话？
sorry.
对不起。
I should say that's my wish.
我应该说 那是我的愿望。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
If you want to be happy,
如果你想幸福，
You shouldn't take commitments so seriously.
你不应该如此认真地对待承诺。
I'm not a good woman.
我不是一个好女人。
I don't know how to play an instrument. I don't know how to memorize poetry.
我不知道如何演奏乐器。 我不知道如何背诗。
I don't know how to help my husband or teach my children.
我不知道如何帮助我的丈夫 或教导孩子。
I couldn’t even make my own wedding dress.
我连自己的婚纱都做不了。
if i get married
如果我结婚了
With a 50-year-old widower,
和50岁的鳏夫一起，
I won't be happy.
我会不高兴的。
You must be feeling terrible, right?
你一定感觉很糟糕吧？
look at your face.
看看你的脸。
Miss He, please don’t!
何小姐，请不要！
Please don't touch me again.
请不要再碰我。
look at your face. You never dared to look me in the eye.
看看你的脸。 你从来不敢直视我的眼睛。
You have a bride like me.
你有一个像我一样的新娘。
What a shame.
实在是太可惜了。
to be honest.
说实话。
you do not like me. It's because you're afraid of me.
你不喜欢我。是怕我。
It is not?
它不是？
It is not? reply.
它不是？回复。
I do not want.
我不想。
You are a nerd.
你是个书呆子。
Everyone says you respect promises and rituals.
每个人都说你 尊重诺言和仪式。
But I think you're just being stubborn.
但我认为你只是固执而已。
looking at you.
看着你。
What can I expect from someone like you?
我能对你这样的人有什么期望呢？
but i can't say
但我不能说
In a place like this.
在这样的地方。
I hate how boring this is.
我讨厌这样太无聊了。
You, an adult, cannot
你，一个成年人，不能
Is it direct and correct?
是否直接且正确？
do not be afraid.
不要害怕。
Did I scare you?
我吓到你了吗？
Let me comfort you.
让我安慰你吧。
Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。
if you could stand up straight
如果你能站直
I said.
我说。
Of course I can.
当然，我可以。
European Union...
欧洲联盟...
they say you are
他们说你是
Expressive and talented.
善于表达，才华横溢。
He is the best young master in Jialin.
他是嘉林最好的少爷。
But you stumble over your words.
但你说话结结巴巴。
How can a person be eloquent?
一个人怎样才能口才好
In front of someone you like?
在你喜欢的人面前？
like?
喜欢？
i liked you
我喜欢过你
long time.
很久。
Take back what you said before speaking again.
收回你说过的话，再说话。
I'll give you another chance.
我再给你一次机会。
I don't give everyone a second chance.
我不会给每个人第二次机会。
Take your time.
不紧不慢。
Think before you speak and speak well.
说话前要三思而后行，说得好。
About our engagement,
关于我们的订婚，
I'm very happy.
我很开心。
Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。
Go away, devil.
走开吧，恶魔。
disappear!
消失！
He is still laughing. I'm sad that he's still laughing.
他还在笑。我很难过， 他还在笑。
If I were to marry a psychic
如果我要嫁给通灵者
generate some spirituality
产生一点灵性
And spend my life witnessing them both
并用我的一生来见证他们俩
Burning turtle shells or counting stars,
龟壳燃烧 或数星星，
I'd rather die.
我宁可死。
In fact, it would be great if our son were a general.
事实上， 如果我们的儿子是一名将军就好了。
Future general.
未来荣将军。
He is your little general Rong.
他就是你们的荣小将军。
What if it's a girl?
如果是女孩怎么办？
So love her as much as you can.
所以尽可能地爱她。
We won't let her go for a day
我们不会放过她一天
Ten is much less.
十个就少得多。
I will never let her face the ordeal of Mount Wuhua.
我绝对不会让她去面对 五华山的磨难。
Maybe I'm late.
也许我迟到了。
But I promise you won't suffer anymore.
但我保证你不会再受苦了。
I will always protect you.
我会永远保护你。
I promise.
我保证。
you?
你？
One poke can knock you out.
一戳就能把你击倒。
You don’t even know how to ride a horse.
你甚至不知道如何骑马。
How dare you promise me? What will you get for me?
你怎么敢答应我？ 你会为我得到什么？
He just said he wanted to have a baby with me.
他只是说 他想和我生个孩子。
I do not want.
我不想要。
Yes.
是的。
What did you say?
你说什么？
General Rong? To love her as much as we can?
容小将军？ 尽我们所能地爱她？
what is that?
那是什么？
As the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion,
作为星象阁的少主，
You don't acknowledge what you said.
你不承认你说的话。
I warn you.
我警告你。
Not only can't I think about it,
不但不能想，
You can't even like me.
你甚至不能喜欢我。
Silta. he. Silta. he.
斯尔塔。他。斯尔塔。他。
Master. I'm late.
少爷。我来晚了。
It was Heshan who wouldn't let me come.
是鹤山不让我来。
If a lady he insults you drunk
如果女士 他辱骂 你喝醉酒
I will never forgive myself.
我永远不会原谅自己。
She won't hurt me.
她不会伤害我。
Flatten, don't worry.
展平，别担心。
Not the future,
不是未来，
Even if she abuses me, please leave her.
即使她 虐待我，也请离开她。
Is this poisoning?
这是中毒了吗？
certainly.
当然。
Just a little narcotic.
只是一点点麻醉剂而已。
Heshan, please ask Mr. He to take her back.
鹤山，求何大人 带她回去。
I can't take her inside.
我不能带她进去。
When the servants saw it, they started talking about it.
仆人们看见了，就会议论纷纷。
Sim.
西姆。
teacher.
老师。
Master Rong sent a message
容师傅发来消息
Miss He was accidentally injured and fainted.
何小姐不慎受伤 ，晕倒了。
He wants you to bring her back.
他希望你能把她带回来。
How did she get injured? Is it serious? Where is she?
她是怎么受伤的？ 很严重吗？她在哪？
Although it was a dart injury, it was not serious.
虽然是飞镖伤， 但并不严重。
Now, she is in the carriage in front of our house.
现在，她就在 我们府前的荣马车里。
ah
啊
Is Mr. Rong taking care of her?
容先生在照顾她吗？
Sim.
西姆。
Then reply to him.
然后回复他。
The person who caused the harm must be held accountable.
造成伤害的人 必须承担责任。
Fortunately he continued to take care of her.
还好他继续照顾她。
OK...
好的...
You can go.
可以去。
Sim.
西姆。
Don't you want to bring Ling back?
不是要把凌带回来吗？
Master Rong and her
容师傅和她
They are not married yet.
他们还没有结婚。
if she was with someone else
如果她和别人在一起的话
I will definitely bring her back.
我一定会把她带回来。
But she was with Master Rong.
但她和容大师在一起。
I'm sure she's fine.
我确信她很好。
also,
此外，
I hope Ling can spend more time with Rong Yu.
希望凌能够有 更多的时间陪伴容羽。
let's go.
我们走吧。
【He is a mansion】
【他是豪宅】
Master, shall we go back now?
少爷，我们现在就回去吧？
Let's go to the courtyard.
我们去庭院吧。
Heshan, you go first.
鹤山，你先。
Remember to fire all servants.
记得解雇所有仆人。
Only one maid remained.
只留下一名女仆。
Sim.
西姆。
Master, come in quickly.
少爷，快进来吧。
Can't stay here all night
不能整晚都留在这里
to avoid gossip.
以避免流言蜚语。
Master, this is what Miss He dropped.
少爷，这是 何小姐掉下来的东西。
Master, I don't want to complain.
少爷，我不想抱怨。
She is dishonest.
她不诚实。
He swore he was burned
他发誓他被烧伤了
Astrology Festival Agenda.
占星节议程。
But it turns out it wasn't her.
但事实证明那不是她。
If I hadn't found him loose
如果我没有 发现他松了
I won't find out.
我不会发现的。
Miss He actually wants
何小姐其实想要
The paintings were secretly printed into prints.
秘密地将画作 印刷成版画。
And keep them forever.
并永远保留它们。
he's good.
他很好。
save.
节省。
Delete and destroy later.
稍后删除并销毁。
But what do we say to women? Well later?
但我们该对女士说什么？嗯稍后？
Let's pretend we don't know.
让我们假装我们不知道。
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
【He is a mansion】
【他是豪宅】
General He,
何将军，
Congratulations on your promotion to first-level general.
恭喜您晋升 为一级上将。
This is a gift from the emperor.
这是皇帝的礼物。
I brought it myself.
我自己带来的。
Thanks.
谢谢。
should ask others
应该问别人
Perform this small task.
执行这个小任务。
You shouldn't bother coming
你不应该费心来
too early.
太早了。
And how to express the emperor's favor?
而如何表达 皇帝的宠爱呢？
The emperor mentioned his daughter
皇帝提到他的女儿
He left his hometown for ten years and only recently returned.
他离开家乡十年了， 最近才回来。
She must not have any aristocratic friends in the capital .
在京城， 她一定没有什么贵族朋友。
For today’s banquet, Xunnan envoy,
为今日宴请 寻南使，
You need to take her with you.
你需要带她一起去。
Maybe she could make friends.
也许她可以交朋友。
return?
还？
she...
她...
General He.
何将军。
Is there anything inappropriate?
有什么不合适的地方吗？
never.
决不。
I express my highest gratitude to His Majesty.
我对陛下致以最崇高的谢意。
About our engagement,
关于我们的订婚，
I'm very happy.
我很开心。
Maybe I'm late,
也许是我迟到了，
But I promise you won't suffer anymore.
但我保证你不会再受苦了。
I will always protect you.
我会永远保护你。
I promise.
我保证。
Azar.
阿扎尔。
Master.
少爷。
some problems?
一些问题？
Don't worry. Just saying.
不用担心。只是说说。
Miss He got up very early
何小姐起得很早
She was very angry.
她非常生气。
As she left the courtyard, she kicked open the door.
当她离开庭院时，她踢开了大门。
Even the stone lion at the door broke its head.
连门口的石狮子都摔断了头。
Many people here know
这里很多人都知道
She spent the night in the yard.
她在院子里过夜。
Is she hurt?
她受伤了吗？
No, but...
不是，但...
When she broke in she was wearing only her nightgown.
当她破门而入时， 她只穿着睡衣。
Rumors may soon spread throughout the capital.
谣言可能 很快就会传遍整个首都。
This is difficult to understand.
这很难理解。
all good.
都好。
I see.
我明白。
Wait a moment.
等一下。
Send a letter to the general's residence.
将一封信送到将军府。
How many times have I said
我说过多少次了
There will be no result between Rong Yu and me.
我和容宇之间不会有结果。
- You - If you don't help me, someone else will.
- 你 - 如果你不帮我，别人会来的
I didn't say that.
我没那么说过。
Ling, go wash up and get dressed.
玲，去洗漱穿衣服吧。
I'll take you to the palace.
我带你去皇宫。
General, the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion has sent news.
将军，星象阁少主 传来消息。
They said it was important.
他们说这很重要。
[To General He] This is a letter from our young master.
[致何将军] 这是我们少爷的一封信。
please read.
请阅读。
Ling,
凌,
There are many rules in the palace.
皇宫里有很多规矩。
Try walking upright.
尝试直立行走。
Place your hands in front of you.
将双手放在前面。
Don't look around, okay?
别东张西望，好吗？
say what needs to be said
说该说的话
And don't say things you shouldn't say.
并且不要说不应该说的话。
I'm going to see the queen.
我要去见女王。
Ling, the palace doesn't feel like home.
凌，皇宫不像家。
Proceed with caution.
谨慎行事。
There is no one to protect her when we are not around.
当我们不在身边时，没有人会保护她。
I see.
我明白。
Ling,
凌,
Have you forgotten what I taught you?
你忘记我教你的了吗？
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
let's go.
我们走吧。
correct.
正确的。
again.
再次。
- Your Highness.
- 殿下。
Cheng'an!
Cheng'an!
Chengan, are you okay?
成安，你还好吗？
Be bold! How dare you hurt the prince?
大胆！ 你怎么敢伤害太子？
Playing badminton is the same as taking turns.
打羽毛球和轮流是一样的。
I'm kidding Your Highness.
我在跟殿下开玩笑。
how dare you?
你怎么敢？
The prince didn't say he wanted to play with you.
太子没说 要跟你玩啊。
all good. Actually I think
都好。其实我觉得
You played shuttlecock very well.
你毽子打得很好。
must. My brother He Qingxing plays better than me.
一定。我哥哥 何庆星弹得比我还好。
My name is He Jiuling.
我叫何九龄。
It turns out that you are the daughter that He Liang sent to Wuhua Mountain to study art.
原来你是何梁送去五华山学艺的女儿啊。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Sim.
西姆。
Hello, Your Majesty.
您好，陛下。
Princess. Crown Prince.
公主。皇太子。
Come and sit down.
过来坐下。
Dad said there are many centipedes and scorpions on Wuhua Mountain.
爸爸说 五华山上有很多蜈蚣、蝎子。
I'm curious.
我很好奇。
Miss He, what did you learn there?
何小姐，你在那里学到了什么？
How about it?
怎么样？
I want to know what you learned in Wuhua Mountain.
我想知道你在五华山学到了什么。
What did it give me?
它给了我什么？
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Your Majesty, please do not panic.
陛下，请不要惊慌。
It's hard to explain in a few words what I learned.
很难用 几句话来解释我学到的东西。
Since Ms. Jiang is very curious,
自从女士 江老师很好奇，
I think it's better for her to go through this on her own.
我认为她自己经历这件事更好。
My master taught me how to make medicine.
我的师父教我如何制药。
my best person
我最擅长的人
It's deodorant pills.
是体香丸。
When you take medicine,
当你服药时，
Its body exudes a light fragrance.
它的身体散发着淡淡的香味。
She is harmless.
她是无害的。
Even so,
即使是这样，
You are too reckless.
你太鲁莽了。
It's really my fault.
这确实是我的错。
It's interesting.
这很有趣。
When will I be able to smell this faint scent?
我什么时候才能闻到这淡淡的味道呢？
logo.
标识。
Why give me such a good thing?
为什么要给我这么好的东西？
Instead of eating it yourself?
而不是自己吃？
Peachy. It's a peach.
桃香。是桃子。
The Crown Prince is my soul mate.
皇太子是我的灵魂伴侣。
The first aroma is peach and the last aroma is citrus.
第一个香气是桃子香气， 最后一个香气是柑橘香气。
The fragrance remains for three days.
香味可以 保留三天。
I will withdraw.
我会撤回。
How dare you taint my cousin.
你竟敢玷污我表弟。
He Jiuling, you have gone too far.
何九菱，你太过分了。
Mom, you should punish her.
妈妈，你应该惩罚她。
Why punish her? She did nothing wrong.
为什么要惩罚她？ 她没有做错任何事。
Curious was our cousin.
好奇的是我们的表弟。
Acho que a He Jiuling
Acho que a He Jiuling
Interesting.
很有意思。
I like her. I want to play with her.
我喜欢她。我想和她一起玩。
Let her come to the palace every day.
让她每天都来王宫。
Your Majesty,
陛下，
The emperor asked the lord and the prince,
皇上问主公 和太子，
And other maids in the palace also came to the banquet.
以及 宫中的其他宫女也都来到了宴会。
affim. Apparently.
肯定。显然。
Jiuling, when you see the emperor,
九龄，当你见到皇上时，
One should not be reckless.
不应该鲁莽。
Otherwise, even I can't protect her.
不然的话，连我都保护不了她。
Sim.
西姆。
The queen is coming.
女王来了。
Where is the pine forest?
松林在哪里？
Why hasn't Pine Forest come yet?
松林怎么还没来？
Tio,
蒂奥，
My cousin was frightened by General He's daughter.
我表弟被何将军的女儿吓到了。
What's there?
那里有什么？
My mom told me not to tell.
我妈妈告诉我不要告诉。
I will tell.
我会告诉。
He Jiuling gave my cousin a pill
何九龄给我表弟一颗药
It can make people 's bodies smell good.
它可以使人 的身体闻起来很香。
Until my cousin got angry.
直到表哥生气了。
Dad, she's so funny.
爸爸，她真有趣。
Can I invite her to play with me more in the future?
以后我可以邀请她 多陪我玩吗？
What might the aromatic smell be?
芳香气味可能是什么？
Why does this anger her?
为什么这会激怒她？
This is because...
这是因为...
Cheng'an
Cheng'an
I don't know either.
我也不知道。
Your Majesty,
陛下，
My daughter grew up in the mountains and doesn’t understand etiquette.
我女儿从小在山里长大 ，不懂礼仪。
If she offends someone,
如果她冒犯了某人，
I am willing to accept punishment.
我愿意接受惩罚。
my Lord,
我的主，
I'm very sorry.
我很抱歉。
General He, how polite!
贺将军，多么有礼貌啊！
please sit down.
请坐下。
General He's daughter is deeply favored by the prince.
何将军的女儿 深得太子宠爱，
The most annoying one is Princess Jialin.
最讨厌的是嘉琳公主。
She must be interesting.
她一定很有趣。
What we are discussing today is
今天我们讨论的是
Jialin formed an alliance with Xunnan.
家林与寻南结盟。
I think it’s better for a woman to marry Xunnan
我觉得女人还是嫁给寻南比较好
Strengthen our relationship, just like the relationship between Qin and Jin.
加强我们的关系， 就像秦晋之间的关系一样。
He is my big brother!
他是我的大哥！
A sirta. he
一位斯尔塔。他
She must be my consort.
她一定是我的驸马。
♫ Under the sunset♫
♫ 黄昏的夕阳下 ♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫我旅行千里之外♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 月光下演奏西塔琴 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 饮料不会让我忘记 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 你默默转身 ，合上结婚簿♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫问天上有多少颗星星♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫我轻轻地弹奏西塔琴 等待像你这样的人♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫最终你 是我不可避免的命运♫